<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yiğit Kolat</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yiğit Kolat</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[difeʁɑ̃s]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/diferas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/diferas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tokyo Philharmonic Orchestra, Kazumasa Watanabe, conductor&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The piece features nine “forces”, nine events whose appearances trigger significant changes in the musical discourse. Among these forces there are simple gestures that extend to the entire orchestral texture, unassuming rhythmic alterations that affect the local pitch structure, or a particular timbral cue that cause similar timbres to emerge. The main function of these forces is to create a seamless formal flow while leaving space for large-scale textural disturbances. This flow can be considered as a constant deferral of meaning through a chain of signifiers, where the listener’s attention is constantly pushed towards the future. Musical semantic depends on a network of references, and every reference to the past creates hierarchies, further emphasizing the differences between the materials. The title of the piece comes from this double-meaning, deferral and difference, embodied in the term différance in Jacques Derrida’s essay bearing the same title.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARN.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/darn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/darn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Luke Fitzpatrick, violin &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Ibidunni Ojikutu, spoken voice&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DARN. exhibits a counterpoint of evolving structures. Perhaps the most prominent of these structures is the spoken part that contains a number of reactions to Kendrick Lamar’s 2018 Pulitzer Prize in Music achievement, collected from various online sources. The reactions are integrated into the piece in a particular order, ranging from seemingly naïve questions about what qualifies Lamar’s album DAMN. for the award, to bursts of blatant racism.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halki / Heybeliada</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/halki_heybeliada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/halki_heybeliada/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Shames, piano&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Halki / Heybeliada is an homage to the Turkish-Armenian composer Edgar Manas (1875-1964), and based on the third piece of his piano album, Les Îles des princes. Each formal unit in the piece stems from a different brief excerpt, a “moment” from the recording of the source work. These excerpts are processed by applying a “databending&amp;quot; method: after digitally converting the sound excerpts into streams of characters, the letters of the word SOYKIRIM (‘Genocide’ in Turkish) are removed from each file. The files are converted into sound files again, introducing a strong distortion due to the removed data. The raw musical material is then extracted from these altered sounds via a custom Music Information Retrieval tool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference Engines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/inference_engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/inference_engines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The title refers to an inference engine as a neural network component both in metaphorical and direct ways. The musical content consists of a guided improvisation session partially driven by the musicians’ inferences on the written material, reflecting the musician mind as a metaphorical inference engine. The score also provides an input for an actual inference engine, generating a fluid video-notation that guides the improvisation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These elements come together within a context that focuses on racially-biased practices in facial recognition applications. Weights from a biased and insufficient dataset are fed into a third inferencing engine that is optimized for real-time audio processing to achieve a distortion effect. A deliberate distancing between the musical process and the sound effect serves to emphasize the essential identity of the distortion as an output of a faulty neural network. Its separate and insistent presence reminds us the very real consequences of using such networks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messenger of Sorrows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/messenger_of_sorrows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/messenger_of_sorrows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;for soprano, bass flute, violin, electric guitar and live electronics&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Inverted Space Ensemble  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Sarah Kolat, soprano  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Daria Binkowski, bass flute  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Luke Fitzpatrick, violin  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Jeff Bowen, e. guitar&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hêjîra çiyayî  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Delala çiyayî     &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Dar hejîrokê   &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Xem revînokê&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fig of the mountains   &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Beauty of the mountains   &lt;br&gt;&#xA;You are the fig tree   &lt;br&gt;&#xA;You are the messenger of sorrows&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Titled after the Kurdish folk song quoted (and loosely translated) above, Messenger of Sorrows utilizes a process that is analogous to that of Alvin Lucier’s I Am Sitting in a Room (1969), in which a repetitive recording/ playing of Lucier narrating a text in a room gradually discloses the resonant frequencies of the very room he was sitting in. The resonances of Messenger of Sorrows, however, come from a room that is being destroyed: all musical materials relate to a single impulse, the sound of a rocket hitting a Kurdish house, recorded by the survivors during the curfew imposed on the southeastern town of Cizre in September 2015 by the Turkish government.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oasis of Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/oasis_of_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/oasis_of_now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Naeim Rahmani, classical guitar     &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Jeff Bowen, electric guitar &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Abbey Blackwell, double bass&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This piece can be considered in two distinct ways:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A meditation on the following lines from Sohrab Sepehri’s poem that carries the same title:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“if you are coming to me / approach gently, softly, lest you crack / the fragile china of my solitude”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A meditation on this “situation”:&#xA;“Musicians have departed to build new lives, leaving their instruments behind. The doctors have done the same, as the teachers, engineers, artists… After drying up all the life-giving flows in this land, what remains to us are the distant echoes of their streams”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quia Ergo Femina</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/quia_ergo_femina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/quia_ergo_femina/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lola Wolf, organ  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;The Monastic Schola of St. Benedict’s Monastery, Janine Mettling, OSB, cond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quia Ergo Femina draws inspiration from an egg-shaped symbolism of the universe depicted in Scivias, a collection of Hildegard von Bingen&amp;rsquo;s visions. The breathing, ever-changing nature of the cosmic egg is reflected in the piece with a series of transformations, projected by the minute actions of the organist. The piece features its namesake, Hildegard von Bingen&amp;rsquo;s psalm antiphon Quia Ergo Femina, further reflecting the egg metaphor by defining itself as a mere vessel that carries the twelfth-century masterpiece at its core.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shōbute</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/shobute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/shobute/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryoko Aoki, Noh-voice  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Ryuji Masumoto, piccolo&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In March 2016, the computer program AlphaGo defeated Lee Se-dol, a South Korean Go player of 9 dan rank in the first game of Google DeepMind Challenge Match. AlphaGo’s victory meant a monumental achievement in the field of artificial intelligence—and immediately revived age-old questions about the nature of artificial and “natural” intelligence. The main inspiration of the piece comes from these unanswered questions.&#xA;The piece is based on two layers of processing, a machine layer and a human layer. The machine layer consists of mapping the data taken from the game log of the Se-dol vs. AlphaGo game into musical parameters and eventually to musical notation, using a custom-written notation software. The Noh-voice is based on the black moves (Se-dol), while the piccolo part is based on the white moves (AlphaGo). The human layer consists of spontaneous repurposing, alteration, and amplification of the machine layer. Additionally, commentaries made about the game by various Go masters both provided the text, and are used to shape the dramatic contour of the music. The machine-human dichotomy, in terms of certainty and uncertainty, or calculation and intuition, also exists in the two modes of performance: each musician uses two types of notations that differ in their communication of how specific the musical result should be. One of these notational systems is based on the yowagin scale that is often employed in Noh theater.&#xA;Shōbute is a Go term, signifying a risky play that is employed in an attempt to bring balance when one is at disadvantage. As a tactic that involves considerable risks, Shōbute is an emotionally charged choice, symbolizing an inherently human aspect of the game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spomenik I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/spomenik_i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/spomenik_i/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rachel Reyes, flute &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Justin Zeitlinger, violin &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Cole Henslee, tuba &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Melissa Wang, vibraphone&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“A concept is a brick. It can be used to build the courthouse of reason. Or it can be thrown through the window.&amp;quot; —Brian Massumi, in Pleasures of Philosophy, a translator’s foreword to Deleuze &amp;amp; Guattari’s A Thousand Plateaus&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spomenik means “monument” in various Slavic languages, which is particularly used for the massive abstract sculptures erected in the Former Yugoslavia countries after WWII. The piece relates to its namesake by depending on a 3D graph, a spomenik, which represents a dataset of musical parameters that is used to train a generative AI process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tierra Arrasada</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/tierra_arrasada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/tierra_arrasada/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah Kolat, narrator  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Evan Smith, alto saxophone  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Jordan Voelker, viola  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Michael Nicolella, electric guitar  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Cristina Valdés, piano  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Bonnie Whiting, percussion and Mesoamerican instrument replicas&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The work is mainly based on two sources, the Mayan creation myth Popol Vuh, and an unclassified CIA document on Operation PBSUCCESS, a covert operation carried out by the CIA that paved the way for the 36-year-long civil war in Guatemala. The source materials are presented directly as narration via the electronic layer. The piece thus can be thought as an aural documentary that is presented within a ritual-like musico-dramatic environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yiğit Kolat’s music draws inspirations and expressions from a wide array of topics ranging from bytebeats to the application and ethics of artificial intelligence in music. The complicated political and social landscape of his native Turkey is a recurring theme in his diverse output. His works have been recognized by a prestigious array of international organizations, including the Tōru Takemitsu Composition Award, the Queen Elisabeth Competition, Bogliasco Foundation, and the Concours International de Composition Henri Dutilleux. His music has been featured throughout the United States, Europe, and Asia by leading ensembles and soloists, among them the Tokyo Philharmonic, Solistes de L’Orchestre de Tours, Donatienne Michel-Dansac, and Pascal Gallois; The Nieuw Ensemble, the Talea Ensemble, and the Argento New Music Project, the Athelas Ensemble, the Presidential Symphony Orchestra of Turkey, Peter Sheppard-Skaerved and Aaron Shorr. His music has been broadcast by the Japan Broadcasting Corporation (NHK) and Turkish Radio Television (TRT).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVAL: Project Description</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/eval-res/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/eval-res/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe&#xA;  src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/research/eval.pdf&#34;&#xA;  width=&#34;100%&#34;&#xA;  height=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;  style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&#xA;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34;&gt;&#xA;  This browser does not display PDFs natively.&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/files/my-score.pdf&#34;&gt;Download instead.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; cellpadding=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Spomenik I&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/research/spomenik-res/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spomenik.png&#34; alt=&#34;spomenik&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;EVAL&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/research/eval-res/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;eval.png&#34; alt=&#34;eval&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;        &#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spomenik I: Project Description</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/spomenik-res/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/spomenik-res/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe&#xA;  src=&#34;https://aimc2024.pubpub.org/pub/o0ltua9f/release/1&#34;&#xA;  width=&#34;100%&#34;&#xA;  height=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;  style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&#xA;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Works</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; cellpadding=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Spomenik I&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/spomenik_i/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spomenik.png&#34; alt=&#34;spomenik&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Oasis of Now&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/oasis_of_now/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;oasis.png&#34; alt=&#34;oasis&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Inference Engines&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/inference_engines/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;inference.png&#34; alt=&#34;inference&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;    &#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Tierra Arrasada&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/tierra_arrasada/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tierra.png&#34; alt=&#34;tierra&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;        &#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Shōbute&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/shobute/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;shobute.png&#34; alt=&#34;shobute&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;DARN.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/darn/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;DARN.png&#34; alt=&#34;DARN&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Quia Ergo Femina&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/quia_ergo_femina/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;quia.png&#34; alt=&#34;quia&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Halki / Heybeliada&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/halki_heybeliada/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;halki.png&#34; alt=&#34;halki_heybeliada&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;    &#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Messenger of Sorrows&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/messenger_of_sorrows/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;messenger.png&#34; alt=&#34;messenger_of_sorrows&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;[difeʁɑ̃s]&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/diferas/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;diferas.png&#34; alt=&#34;diferas&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;K&#39;iin&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/kiin/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;kiin.png&#34; alt=&#34;k&#39;iin&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;poppyfield&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/gelincik_tarlasi/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;gelincik.png&#34; alt=&#34;gelincik&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Piano Concerto&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/piano_concerto/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;concerto.png&#34; alt=&#34;piano_concerto&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Exlibris&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/exlibris/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;exlibris.png&#34; alt=&#34;exlibris&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Tülbend&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/tulbend/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tulbend.png&#34; alt=&#34;tulbend&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Yoshin&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/yoshin/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;yoshin.png&#34; alt=&#34;K&#39;iin&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Echoes of Tinder&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/kav_yankilari/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;kav.png&#34; alt=&#34;kav&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td width=&#34;20&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer cell --&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;overlay-text&#34;&gt;Der Untergeher&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/works/der_untergeher/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;untergeher.png&#34; alt=&#34;untergeher&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;300&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;    &#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr style=&#34;height: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;!-- Spacer row --&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
